<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on rickshf</title><link>https://rickshf.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on rickshf</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rickshf.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installing Python</title><link>https://rickshf.github.io/tutorials/install-python/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rickshf.github.io/tutorials/install-python/</guid><description>Python is a popular programming language used in many areas of software development. This tutorial outlines the basic steps to install Python on common operating systems.
Windows Visit the Python downloads page. Download the latest Windows installer. Run the installer and make sure to enable Add Python to PATH. Follow the installation wizard to complete the setup. macOS The easiest method is to install the latest package from the Python downloads page.</description></item><item><title>Introdução à Teoria de Conjuntos</title><link>https://rickshf.github.io/tutorials/teoria-conjuntos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rickshf.github.io/tutorials/teoria-conjuntos/</guid><description>A Teoria de Conjuntos é o ramo da matemática que estuda coleções de objetos, chamados de conjuntos. Cada objeto é chamado de elemento e indicamos que um elemento pertence a um conjunto escrevendo $a \in A$.
Conjuntos e Subconjuntos Um conjunto pode ser definido listando seus elementos, por exemplo: $$A = {1, 2, 3}.$$ Um conjunto $B$ é subconjunto de $A$ (escrevemos $B \subseteq A$) se todo elemento de $B$ também pertencer a $A$.</description></item><item><title>Thank you page for tutorial series</title><link>https://rickshf.github.io/tutorials/thank-you/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rickshf.github.io/tutorials/thank-you/</guid><description>Want to say thank you? Presumably you&amp;rsquo;ve found this page because an article, tutorial, or other resource on this website was useful to you, and you wanted to say thank you.
In that case thank you, I very much appreciate it! You could:
Send me an email! Seriously, if something on this website helped you, it will make my day to know. I love hearing from readers, and you&amp;rsquo;ll almost certainly get a message back from me.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://rickshf.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rickshf.github.io/about/</guid><description>About me And here is some information about me: I'm Brazilian and grew up between Arujá and Jacareí. I've worked professionally at a metallurgy company as a production operator and with electrostatic painting. Since graduating high school, I've also worked as a tutor, including as a freelancer, to help people learn math and programming; recently, I'm also adding web development to my professional skillset. Hobbies include: Big fan of mountain biking and cycling in general.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://rickshf.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rickshf.github.io/contact/</guid><description> Contact me You can reach me by email at almeidah1945@gmail.com.
I love hearing from readers, and you'll almost certainly get a message back from me. If you feel like it, drop me a few lines about your background and/or how you found this site—I'm always interested to hear!</description></item><item><title>License</title><link>https://rickshf.github.io/license/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rickshf.github.io/license/</guid><description>License This website is dual-licensed: Original writing and media (e.g. tutorials, PDF documents, Markdown files, images, and videos) are licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License. Original code (e.g. the HTML, CSS, and JavaScript used to build this website) is licensed under the GNU General Public License v3.0. I want to use this website, what should I do? (IANAL) Here is the website's source code. Please read tldrLegal's summary of the CC BY-NC-SA 4.</description></item><item><title>Content</title><link>https://rickshf.github.io/content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rickshf.github.io/content/</guid><description> Tutorials Installing Python Tutorial on how to install Python on Windows, macOS and Linux. Teoria dos Conjuntos Teoria dos Conjuntos estuda coleções de objetos, chamados conjuntos, e as relações entre eles, como união, interseção e pertinência. Projects</description></item></channel></rss>